{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947903788924","data":{"timestamp":" 947903788924"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_75","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904004888","data":{"timestamp":" 947904004888"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904004950","data":{"timestamp":" 947904004950"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 6037f59e-43a0-44bd-8bd7-abb5468473af"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_75"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifuta vumbi na kukiweka ndani ya gunia lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904015866","data":{"timestamp":" 947904015866"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904016918","data":{"timestamp":" 947904016917"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904019466","data":{"timestamp":" 947904019466"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904020515","data":{"timestamp":" 947904020515"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904023825","data":{"timestamp":" 947904023824"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904024869","data":{"timestamp":" 947904024869"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904027619","data":{"timestamp":" 947904027618"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904029412","data":{"timestamp":" 947904029412"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904032170","data":{"timestamp":" 947904032170"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904033822","data":{"timestamp":" 947904033822"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904036621","data":{"timestamp":" 947904036620"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904036690","data":{"timestamp":" 947904036690"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904037712","data":{"timestamp":" 947904037711"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904040286","data":{"timestamp":" 947904040286"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904042722","data":{"timestamp":" 947904042722"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904044372","data":{"timestamp":" 947904044372"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904046968","data":{"timestamp":" 947904046967"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904048012","data":{"timestamp":" 947904048012"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904051658","data":{"timestamp":" 947904051657"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904052707","data":{"timestamp":" 947904052707"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904055652","data":{"timestamp":" 947904055651"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904056705","data":{"timestamp":" 947904056705"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904060247","data":{"timestamp":" 947904060247"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904061283","data":{"timestamp":" 947904061283"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904065247","data":{"timestamp":" 947904065247"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904066286","data":{"timestamp":" 947904066285"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904069207","data":{"timestamp":" 947904069207"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904070250","data":{"timestamp":" 947904070250"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904072752","data":{"timestamp":" 947904072752"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904073226","data":{"timestamp":" 947904073226"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904073944","data":{"timestamp":" 947904073944"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904075199","data":{"timestamp":" 947904075199"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904076301","data":{"timestamp":" 947904076301"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904078639","data":{"timestamp":" 947904078639"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904081529","data":{"timestamp":" 947904081529"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904081663","data":{"timestamp":" 947904081663"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904082616","data":{"timestamp":" 947904082616"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904085053","data":{"timestamp":" 947904085052"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904088379","data":{"timestamp":" 947904088379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904089417","data":{"timestamp":" 947904089417"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904092471","data":{"timestamp":" 947904092471"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904093510","data":{"timestamp":" 947904093509"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904096491","data":{"timestamp":" 947904096491"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904096741","data":{"timestamp":" 947904096741"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904097572","data":{"timestamp":" 947904097572"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904100115","data":{"timestamp":" 947904100115"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904103445","data":{"timestamp":" 947904103445"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904103509","data":{"timestamp":" 947904103509"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904114048","data":{"timestamp":" 947904114047"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0c242466-182f-493f-b59b-c7f4994c184e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904123661","data":{"timestamp":" 947904123661"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0939361c-c372-4231-9dee-fccf91566e65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904127277","data":{"timestamp":" 947904127276"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0939361c-c372-4231-9dee-fccf91566e65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904132969","data":{"timestamp":" 947904132968"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0939361c-c372-4231-9dee-fccf91566e65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904139778","data":{"timestamp":" 947904139778"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0939361c-c372-4231-9dee-fccf91566e65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904143937","data":{"timestamp":" 947904143936"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0939361c-c372-4231-9dee-fccf91566e65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904153358","data":{"timestamp":" 947904153358"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 0939361c-c372-4231-9dee-fccf91566e65"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904162237","data":{"timestamp":" 947904162237"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904164300","data":{"timestamp":" 947904164300"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904166409","data":{"timestamp":" 947904166408"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904169662","data":{"timestamp":" 947904169661"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904171962","data":{"timestamp":" 947904171961"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904174258","data":{"timestamp":" 947904174257"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904177161","data":{"timestamp":" 947904177160"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904179408","data":{"timestamp":" 947904179407"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904181588","data":{"timestamp":" 947904181587"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904184823","data":{"timestamp":" 947904184823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904186965","data":{"timestamp":" 947904186965"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904189002","data":{"timestamp":" 947904189002"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904191891","data":{"timestamp":" 947904191891"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904194055","data":{"timestamp":" 947904194055"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904196237","data":{"timestamp":" 947904196237"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904199192","data":{"timestamp":" 947904199192"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904201493","data":{"timestamp":" 947904201493"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904203774","data":{"timestamp":" 947904203774"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904206719","data":{"timestamp":" 947904206718"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904208782","data":{"timestamp":" 947904208782"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904210858","data":{"timestamp":" 947904210858"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904213885","data":{"timestamp":" 947904213885"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904216002","data":{"timestamp":" 947904216001"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904218147","data":{"timestamp":" 947904218147"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904221243","data":{"timestamp":" 947904221243"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904223592","data":{"timestamp":" 947904223592"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904225954","data":{"timestamp":" 947904225953"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904229090","data":{"timestamp":" 947904229090"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904231378","data":{"timestamp":" 947904231377"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904233618","data":{"timestamp":" 947904233618"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904236509","data":{"timestamp":" 947904236509"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904238683","data":{"timestamp":" 947904238683"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904240910","data":{"timestamp":" 947904240910"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904243924","data":{"timestamp":" 947904243923"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904246302","data":{"timestamp":" 947904246302"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904248599","data":{"timestamp":" 947904248599"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904251663","data":{"timestamp":" 947904251663"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904254017","data":{"timestamp":" 947904254017"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904256351","data":{"timestamp":" 947904256351"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904259234","data":{"timestamp":" 947904259234"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904261450","data":{"timestamp":" 947904261449"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904263682","data":{"timestamp":" 947904263682"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904266839","data":{"timestamp":" 947904266838"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904269106","data":{"timestamp":" 947904269106"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904271323","data":{"timestamp":" 947904271323"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904274574","data":{"timestamp":" 947904274574"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904276991","data":{"timestamp":" 947904276990"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904279374","data":{"timestamp":" 947904279374"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904282159","data":{"timestamp":" 947904282158"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904284313","data":{"timestamp":" 947904284313"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904286441","data":{"timestamp":" 947904286441"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904289775","data":{"timestamp":" 947904289774"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904292094","data":{"timestamp":" 947904292092"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904294357","data":{"timestamp":" 947904294356"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904297470","data":{"timestamp":" 947904297470"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904299762","data":{"timestamp":" 947904299762"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904302044","data":{"timestamp":" 947904302044"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904305047","data":{"timestamp":" 947904305047"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904307179","data":{"timestamp":" 947904307178"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904309340","data":{"timestamp":" 947904309339"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904312493","data":{"timestamp":" 947904312492"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904314786","data":{"timestamp":" 947904314785"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904317072","data":{"timestamp":" 947904317071"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904320308","data":{"timestamp":" 947904320307"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904322518","data":{"timestamp":" 947904322517"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904324744","data":{"timestamp":" 947904324743"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904328023","data":{"timestamp":" 947904328023"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904330365","data":{"timestamp":" 947904330364"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904332711","data":{"timestamp":" 947904332710"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904335831","data":{"timestamp":" 947904335831"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904338170","data":{"timestamp":" 947904338170"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904340530","data":{"timestamp":" 947904340529"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904343954","data":{"timestamp":" 947904343953"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904344072","data":{"timestamp":" 947904344072"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904360678","data":{"timestamp":" 947904360677"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 3e0fd798-0088-44a0-8501-b121c135d802"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904371528","data":{"timestamp":" 947904371527"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jasho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904378358","data":{"timestamp":" 947904378358"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jasho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904379926","data":{"timestamp":" 947904379926"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904383095","data":{"timestamp":" 947904383095"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904384645","data":{"timestamp":" 947904384644"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" JEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904390999","data":{"timestamp":" 947904390999"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904392574","data":{"timestamp":" 947904392574"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904395522","data":{"timestamp":" 947904395522"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904397069","data":{"timestamp":" 947904397069"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904400024","data":{"timestamp":" 947904400024"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904401583","data":{"timestamp":" 947904401583"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jikoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904405033","data":{"timestamp":" 947904405033"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jikoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904406584","data":{"timestamp":" 947904406584"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904410352","data":{"timestamp":" 947904410351"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904411900","data":{"timestamp":" 947904411900"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904415056","data":{"timestamp":" 947904415056"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904416617","data":{"timestamp":" 947904416617"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904419021","data":{"timestamp":" 947904419021"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904421028","data":{"timestamp":" 947904421028"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904421100","data":{"timestamp":" 947904421100"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" ade438f6-f0d6-4d97-a17a-7278868d0600"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904433505","data":{"timestamp":" 947904433505"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jasho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904437227","data":{"timestamp":" 947904437227"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jasho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904438776","data":{"timestamp":" 947904438776"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904442074","data":{"timestamp":" 947904442074"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904443631","data":{"timestamp":" 947904443631"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" JEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904448421","data":{"timestamp":" 947904448421"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904449983","data":{"timestamp":" 947904449983"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904452381","data":{"timestamp":" 947904452380"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904453946","data":{"timestamp":" 947904453946"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904456150","data":{"timestamp":" 947904456150"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904457709","data":{"timestamp":" 947904457709"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jikoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904462638","data":{"timestamp":" 947904462637"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jikoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904464198","data":{"timestamp":" 947904464198"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904468562","data":{"timestamp":" 947904468562"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904470120","data":{"timestamp":" 947904470120"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904473674","data":{"timestamp":" 947904473674"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904475230","data":{"timestamp":" 947904475230"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904481271","data":{"timestamp":" 947904481271"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904483280","data":{"timestamp":" 947904483280"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904483443","data":{"timestamp":" 947904483443"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" c52c543e-12bc-415c-9a9d-1c7bb9d1e006"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904497849","data":{"timestamp":" 947904497849"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jasho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904500332","data":{"timestamp":" 947904500332"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jasho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904501868","data":{"timestamp":" 947904501868"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904506329","data":{"timestamp":" 947904506329"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904507919","data":{"timestamp":" 947904507919"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" JEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904512231","data":{"timestamp":" 947904512231"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" START_JEKUNDU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904514547","data":{"timestamp":" 947904514547"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904516096","data":{"timestamp":" 947904516096"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904518626","data":{"timestamp":" 947904518626"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904520228","data":{"timestamp":" 947904520228"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904522339","data":{"timestamp":" 947904522338"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904523899","data":{"timestamp":" 947904523898"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jikoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904527349","data":{"timestamp":" 947904527349"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jikoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904528906","data":{"timestamp":" 947904528906"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904534553","data":{"timestamp":" 947904534553"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904536107","data":{"timestamp":" 947904536107"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904541203","data":{"timestamp":" 947904541203"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904542753","data":{"timestamp":" 947904542753"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904547816","data":{"timestamp":" 947904547816"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904549830","data":{"timestamp":" 947904549830"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904549994","data":{"timestamp":" 947904549994"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904557457","data":{"timestamp":" 947904557456"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" d25dc097-7e78-44ac-b607-d575e797beb9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904567147","data":{"timestamp":" 947904567146"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904567528","data":{"timestamp":" 947904567527"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904568022","data":{"timestamp":" 947904568021"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904568371","data":{"timestamp":" 947904568371"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904568785","data":{"timestamp":" 947904568785"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904569259","data":{"timestamp":" 947904569259"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904569482","data":{"timestamp":" 947904569482"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904572654","data":{"timestamp":" 947904572654"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904572687","data":{"timestamp":" 947904572686"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904573411","data":{"timestamp":" 947904573410"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904573814","data":{"timestamp":" 947904573814"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904574121","data":{"timestamp":" 947904574121"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904574331","data":{"timestamp":" 947904574331"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904574532","data":{"timestamp":" 947904574531"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904574852","data":{"timestamp":" 947904574852"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904575083","data":{"timestamp":" 947904575082"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904578322","data":{"timestamp":" 947904578322"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904578730","data":{"timestamp":" 947904578730"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904581316","data":{"timestamp":" 947904581316"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904581530","data":{"timestamp":" 947904581530"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904581740","data":{"timestamp":" 947904581740"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904585240","data":{"timestamp":" 947904585239"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904589021","data":{"timestamp":" 947904589021"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904590052","data":{"timestamp":" 947904590052"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904592799","data":{"timestamp":" 947904592798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904593181","data":{"timestamp":" 947904593181"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904593674","data":{"timestamp":" 947904593673"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904594027","data":{"timestamp":" 947904594026"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904594436","data":{"timestamp":" 947904594436"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904594924","data":{"timestamp":" 947904594924"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904595159","data":{"timestamp":" 947904595158"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904598373","data":{"timestamp":" 947904598373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904598418","data":{"timestamp":" 947904598416"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904599140","data":{"timestamp":" 947904599140"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904599548","data":{"timestamp":" 947904599548"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904599849","data":{"timestamp":" 947904599849"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904600052","data":{"timestamp":" 947904600052"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904600245","data":{"timestamp":" 947904600244"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904600557","data":{"timestamp":" 947904600557"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904600780","data":{"timestamp":" 947904600780"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904603474","data":{"timestamp":" 947904603473"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904603568","data":{"timestamp":" 947904603568"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904618348","data":{"timestamp":" 947904618347"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904623829","data":{"timestamp":" 947904623829"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904661204","data":{"timestamp":" 947904661203"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" f61cd4a2-2e0a-42bd-a93d-5fb8c7e7c6f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904661260","data":{"timestamp":" 947904661260"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 57716a43-c5f5-4419-858f-5f904a16a21f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_74"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Apenyo alikuwa msichana mrembo na kila mwanamume alitaka kumwoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWOA"," userResponse":" KUMWOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904670387","data":{"timestamp":" 947904670387"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 57716a43-c5f5-4419-858f-5f904a16a21f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_74"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Apenyo alikuwa msichana mrembo na kila mwanamume alitaka kumwoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904678013","data":{"timestamp":" 947904678013"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 57716a43-c5f5-4419-858f-5f904a16a21f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_74"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Apenyo alikuwa msichana mrembo na kila mwanamume alitaka kumwoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904684099","data":{"timestamp":" 947904684099"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 57716a43-c5f5-4419-858f-5f904a16a21f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_74"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Apenyo alikuwa msichana mrembo na kila mwanamume alitaka kumwoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904691496","data":{"timestamp":" 947904691496"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 57716a43-c5f5-4419-858f-5f904a16a21f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_74"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Apenyo alikuwa msichana mrembo na kila mwanamume alitaka kumwoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904698867","data":{"timestamp":" 947904698867"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 57716a43-c5f5-4419-858f-5f904a16a21f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_74"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Apenyo alikuwa msichana mrembo na kila mwanamume alitaka kumwoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904708952","data":{"timestamp":" 947904708951"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 57716a43-c5f5-4419-858f-5f904a16a21f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_74"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Apenyo alikuwa msichana mrembo na kila mwanamume alitaka kumwoa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904718716","data":{"timestamp":" 947904718715"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 07f6da80-40e3-48e4-8307-e89ff32f411b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-e-k"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904724284","data":{"timestamp":" 947904724283"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 07f6da80-40e3-48e4-8307-e89ff32f411b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-e-k"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904729776","data":{"timestamp":" 947904729776"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 07f6da80-40e3-48e4-8307-e89ff32f411b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-e-k"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904733445","data":{"timestamp":" 947904733445"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 07f6da80-40e3-48e4-8307-e89ff32f411b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_s-j-a"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904736927","data":{"timestamp":" 947904736927"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 07f6da80-40e3-48e4-8307-e89ff32f411b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_h-d-j"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904741558","data":{"timestamp":" 947904741558"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 07f6da80-40e3-48e4-8307-e89ff32f411b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_s-j-t"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904765447","data":{"timestamp":" 947904765447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 07f6da80-40e3-48e4-8307-e89ff32f411b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_k-y-j"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904786855","data":{"timestamp":" 947904786855"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 07f6da80-40e3-48e4-8307-e89ff32f411b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_m-j-e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947904788687","data":{"timestamp":" 947904788687"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000115_053538"," gameId":" 07f6da80-40e3-48e4-8307-e89ff32f411b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_j_m-j-e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}